oklahomacounty.org 2015-12-06

# Oklahoma County - Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the Oklahoma County web site and reviewing our privacy policy. We will collect no personal information about you unless the information is voluntarily provided by you.

Thank you for visiting the Oklahoma County web site and reviewing our privacy policy. We will collect no personal information about you unless the information is voluntarily provided by you. 

Information Collected Automatically 

Through the use of powerful online tools available on our web site, Oklahoma County is committed to providing the public with an enjoyable online experience. While providing this service we are also committed to protecting users from the unexpected use of personally identifiable information. In an effort to continue to provide users with a quality online experience, Oklahoma County uses server log analysis tools to track web site usage. These monthly summaries provide statistics such as: 

  * Number of hits
  * Most and least popular pages
  * IP addresses and domains
  * Most and least active days
  * Technical statistics
  * Referrers and keywords
  * Browsers and platforms

Information Provided by You

Visitors have the option to voluntarily provide Oklahoma County with additional information through the Oklahoma County web site. Oklahoma County will retain information volunteered by the user, such as e-mail addresses, telephone numbers, registration information, etc. This will be used by the county as a means to communicate with the user if appropriate, and will only be shared with other government agencies if your inquiry relates to that agency or as otherwise required by law. This information will not be shared with outside commercial entities. 

If during your visit to our web site you participate by completing and submitting an online form or survey or send an e-mail message, the following additional information will be collected: 

  * The email address and contents of the e-mail, for those who communicate with us via e-mail.
  * Information volunteered in response to a survey.
  * Information volunteered through an online form for any other purpose.

The information collected is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video, and graphic information formats that you send us. 

Users are cautioned that the collection of personal information requested or volunteered by children online or by e-mail will be treated the same as information given by an adult and may be subject to public access. If we discover or are otherwise notified that we have received any such information from a child in violation of this policy, we will delete that information. If you believe that Oklahoma County has collected information from or about a child under the age of thirteen, please contact us immediately. 

Cookies

To provide better service to our users we may use "cookies" to customize your browsing experience. A cookie is a small text file stored on a user's computer, created and subsequently read by a web site server. Cookies created on your computer by using this web site do not reveal information that you have not supplied, therefore your privacy or security is not compromised. By tracking usage of cookies, we can best determine the needs of our users.

Several of the most recent web browsers can notify you before a web site places a cookie on your computer. Some browsers allow you to block, individually accept, or reject any particular cookie. Although it is good practice to periodically check and delete cookie files in the manner suitable for the browser you are using, you must allow your browser to accept cookies to be able to use certain Oklahoma County online systems. If cookies are disabled or a "cookie cruncher" is running on your client computer, you will get errors when trying to use applications that use cookies. 

Links to Other Sites

Our web site has links to other government agencies as well as links to other organizations. Oklahoma County does not endorse their web policies, products, or services. Once you have linked to another site you are subject to the privacy policy of the new site.

Security

Oklahoma County has taken several steps to safeguard the integrity of its data and prevent unauthorized access to information maintained by the county. These measures are designed and intended to prevent corruption of data, block unknown or unauthorized access to our systems and information, and to provide reasonable protection of private information in our possession. This information should not be construed in any way as giving business, legal, or other advice, or warrant as fail proof, the security of information provided via the Oklahoma County web site.

Oklahoma County Contact Information

For information about your personal information collection and its use or to offer comments about Oklahoma County's web site, contact:

Oklahoma County Information Technology  
320 S. Robert S Kerr, Suite 321  
Oklahoma City, OK 73102  
Phone: (405) 713-1349
